A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1950
  - Spain, 1950; 1950/795
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/795.A
      - Spain, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
    - Spain - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/795.E
      - Spain, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3379)
  - Sweden, 1950; 1950/800
    - Sweden, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3380)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/800.A
      - Sweden, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3380)
    - Sweden - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 1950/800.D
      - Sweden, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3380)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/800.E
      - Sweden, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3380)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/800.S
      - Sweden, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3380)
  - Switzerland, 1950; 1950/803
    - Switzerland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3381)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/803.A
      - Switzerland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3381)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3381)
  - Near East Region, 1950; 1950/804
    - Near East, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3382)
    - Near East Region - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/804.A
      - Near East, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3382)
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/804.R
      - Near East, 1950 (Box 505, Folder 3382)
      - Marshall, John - Diary of Trip to Near East, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3383)
  - Turkey, 1950; 1950/805
    - Turkey, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 1950; 1950/805.C
      - Turkey, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/805.E
      - Turkey, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/805.R
      - Turkey, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
  - Cyprus, 1950; 1950/809
    - Cyprus, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
  - Israel, 1950; 1950/825
    - Israel, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/825.A
      - Israel, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Israel - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/825.E
      - Israel, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
    - Israel - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 1950/825.R
      - Israel, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3384)
  - Lebanon, 1950; 1950/833
    - Lebanon, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3385)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1950; 1950/833.A
      - Lebanon, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3385)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1950; 1950/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3385)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 1950/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3385)
    - Lebanon - Social Sciences, 1950; 1950/833.S
      - Lebanon, 1950 (Box 506, Folder 3385)
- General Correspondence, 1951
  - International, 1951; 1951/100
    - Staff - International - Aitken, Thomas H. G., 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3386)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richmond K., 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3387)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richmond K., 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3388)
    - Staff - International - Bates, Marston - Publications, 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3389)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, Marshall C. - Publications - Barnard, Chester I., 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3390)
    - Staff - International - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3391)
    - Staff - International - Bugher, John C. - Burden, Robert P., 1951 (Box 507, Folder 3392)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3393)
    - Staff - International - Carter, Joseph C. - Causey, Ottis R. - D'Arms, Edward F., 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3394)
    - Staff - International - Devinney, Leland S. - Diplomatic Services - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3395)
    - Staff - International - Elmendorf, John E. - Evans, Roger F., 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3396)
    - Staff - International - Fahs, Charles B., 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3397)
    - Staff - International - Fly Study Project, 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3398)
    - Staff - International - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1951 (Box 508, Folder 3399)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B., 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3400)
    - Staff - International - Gregg, Alan - Haddow, A. J. - Publications - Hahn, Richard G. - Publications, 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3401)
    - Staff - International - Hayes, Guy S., 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3402)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B. - Hirst, Esther Mary, 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3403)
    - Staff - International - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3404)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H. - Johnson, Harold N., 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3405)
    - Staff - International - Kendrick, John F. - Kerr, J. Austin, 1951 (Box 509, Folder 3406)
    - Staff - International - Kimball, Lindsley F. - Kitchen, Stuart F., 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3407)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A., 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3408)
    - Staff - International - Loomis, William F. - Lumsden, W. H. R. - Publications, 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3409)
    - Staff - International - McCoy, Oliver R., 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3410)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, William A., 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3411)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, William A., 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3412)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John - Publications, 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3413)
    - Staff - International - Mailing Lists, 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3414)
    - Staff - International - Marshall, John, 1951 (Box 510, Folder 3415)
    - Staff - International - Miller, Harry M. - Morison, Robert S. - Noll, Anna Mary, 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3416)
    - Staff - International - Oliver, Wade - Payne, George C. - Peterson, Osler L. - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Rhind, Flora M., 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3417)
    - Staff - International - Rickard, E. R. - Publications, 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3418)
    - Staff - International - Russell, Paul F. - 1, 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3419)
    - Staff - International - Russell, Paul F. - 2 - Publications, 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3420)
    - Staff - International - Ryan, Bryce - Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith, Hugh H., 1951 (Box 511, Folder 3421)
    - Staff - International - Smithburn, Kenneth C. - Publications - Strode, George K., 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3422)
    - Staff - International - Taylor, Richard M., 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3423)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3424)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3425)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3426)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 512, Folder 3427)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3428)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3429)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - Social Sciences, 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3430)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-P), 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3431)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (Q-Z), 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3432)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - W. H. O., 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3433)
    - Staff - International - Warren, Andrew J., 1951 (Box 513, Folder 3434)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B., 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3435)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B., 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3436)
    - Staff - International - Weaver, Warren - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3437)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M., 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3438)
    - Staff - International - Willits, Joseph H. - Wilson, D. Bruce, 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3439)
    - Staff - International - World Institute, 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3440)
    - Staff - International - Worth, C. Brooke - Publications, 1951 (Box 514, Folder 3441)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (A-Ec), 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3442)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Ed-Inf), 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3443)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Int-Pop), 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3444)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Pub-Tay), 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3445)
    - Staff - International - Miscellany - (Th-Z), 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3446)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/100.A
      - Staff - International, 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3447)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1951; 1951/100.O
      - Staff - International, 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3447)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/100.S
      - Staff - International, 1951 (Box 515, Folder 3447)
  - United States, 1951; 1951/200
    - United States - (A-Am), 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3448)
    - United States - (American A-B), 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3449)
    - United States - (American Book Publishers Council), 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3450)
    - United States - (American C), 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3451)
    - United States - American Council on Education, 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3452)
    - United States - (American D-I), 1951 (Box 516, Folder 3453)
    - United States - (American J-Z), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3454)
    - United States - (American J-Z), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3455)
    - United States - (American J-Z), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3456)
    - United States - (An-Av), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3457)
    - United States - (Ba-Bl), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3458)
    - United States - (Bo-Bz), 1951 (Box 517, Folder 3459)
    - United States - (Ca-Car), 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3460)
    - United States - Carnegie - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3461)
    - United States - Carter and Jones, 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3462)
    - United States - (Ce-Col), 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3463)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3465)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3464)
    - United States - Columbia University - Seminars - 1, 1951 (Box 518, Folder 3466)
    - United States - Columbia University - Seminars - 2, 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3467)
    - United States - (Com-Coo), 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3468)
    - United States - Cornell University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3469)
    - United States - Corning Glass Works, 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3470)
    - United States - (Cor-Cz), 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3471)
    - United States - (D-Do), 1951 (Box 519, Folder 3472)
    - United States - (Dr-Du), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3473)
    - United States - Economic Cooperation Administration - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3474)
    - United States - (E), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3475)
    - United States - (Fa), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3476)
    - United States - (Fe-Fon), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3477)
    - United States - (For-Foz), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3478)
    - United States - (F-Fz), 1951 (Box 520, Folder 3479)
    - United States - (G), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3480)
    - United States - (Ha-Har), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3481)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-L), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3482)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-L), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3483)
    - United States - Harvard University - (M-Sch), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3484)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Sh-Z), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3485)
    - United States - (Has-Hz), 1951 (Box 521, Folder 3486)
    - United States - (I-Institute I), 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3487)
    - United States - Institute of International Education, 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3488)
    - United States - (Institute M-Tz), 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3489)
    - United States - International Water Corporation, 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3490)
    - United States - (J-K), 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3491)
    - United States - (J-K), 1951 (Box 522, Folder 3492)
    - United States - (L), 1951 (Box 523, Folder 3493)
    - United States - (Ma), 1951 (Box 523, Folder 3494)
    - United States - (Mc-Me), 1951 (Box 523, Folder 3495)
    - United States - (Mi), 1951 (Box 523, Folder 3496)
    - United States - (Mo-Mz), 1951 (Box 523, Folder 3497)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3498)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3499)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3500)
    - United States - (Na-Ne), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3501)
    - United States - New Jersey Medical College, 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3502)
    - United States - New York - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3503)
    - United States - (Ni-Nz), 1951 (Box 524, Folder 3504)
    - United States - (O-Pa), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3505)
    - United States - (Pan American: A-Z), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3506)
    - United States - (Pap-Per), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3507)
    - United States - Permanente Hospitals, 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3508)
    - United States - Permanente Hospitals - Supplementary Material, 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3509)
    - United States - (Per-Pr), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3510)
    - United States - Princeton - (A-Or), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3511)
    - United States - Princeton - (Os-Z), 1951 (Box 525, Folder 3512)
    - United States - (Pr-Ps), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3512a)
    - United States - (Pu-Pz), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3513)
    - United States - (Ra-Roc), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3514)
    - United States - (Rod-Rz), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3515)
    - United States - (Sa), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3516)
    - United States - (Sc-Se), 1951 (Box 526, Folder 3517)
    - United States - (Sh-Sn), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3518)
    - United States - (So-Sta), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3519)
    - United States - Stanford University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3520)
    - United States - (Sta-Sz), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3521)
    - United States - (T-To), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3522)
    - United States - (Tr-Un), 1951 (Box 527, Folder 3523)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee 1951 Report: Medical Mission to Japan (Box 527, Folder 3524)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee: 1951 Report of the Public Health Planning Team to Germany (Box 528, Folder 3525)
    - United States - (US: A-P), 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3526)
    - United States - Public Health Service, 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3527)
    - United States - (US: R-S), 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3528)
    - United States - State Department - (A-F), 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3529)
    - United States - State Department - Far Eastern Affairs, 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3530)
    - United States - State Department - Foreign Policy Conferences, 1951 (Box 528, Folder 3531)
    - United States - State Department - (G-Z), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3532)
    - United States - University of California - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3533)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3534)
    - United States - University - (D-O), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3535)
    - United States - University - (D-O), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3536)
    - United States - University of Pennsylvania - (A-P), 1951 (Box 529, Folder 3537)
    - United States - University of Pennsylvania - (R-Z), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3538)
    - United States - University - (P-Z), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3539)
    - United States - University - (P-Z), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3540)
    - United States - (V), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3541)
    - United States - (Wa-We), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3542)
    - United States - (Wh-Wr), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3543)
    - United States - (X-Z), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3544)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/200.A
      - United States - (A-J), 1951 (Box 530, Folder 3545)
      - United States - (M-O), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3546)
      - United States - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3547)
      - United States - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3548)
      - United States - (W-Z), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3549)
    - United States - Nursing, 1951; 1951/200.C
      - United States - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3550)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3551)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/200.D
      - United States, 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3552)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/200.E
      - United States, 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3552)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1951; 1951/200.L
      - United States, 1951 (Box 531, Folder 3552)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/200.R
      - United States - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3553)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3554)
      - United States - University (A-Z), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3555)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/200.S
      - United States - (A-R), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3556)
      - United States - SSRC - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3557)
      - United States - (Sy-Z), 1951 (Box 532, Folder 3558)
  - California, 1951; 1951/205
    - California, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1951; 1951/206
    - Canal Zone, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Florida, 1951; 1951/211
    - Florida, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Guam, 1951; 1951/213
    - Guam, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Hawaii, 1951; 1951/214
    - Hawaii, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
    - Hawaii - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/214.D
      - Hawaii, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Illinois, 1951; 1951/216
    - Illinois, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - Mississippi, 1951; 1951/222
    - Mississippi, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3559)
  - New York, 1951; 1951/235
    - New York, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
  - North Carolina, 1951; 1951/236
    - North Carolina, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
  - Philippines, 1951; 1951/242
    - Philippines, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/242.A
      - Philippines, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1951; 1951/242.C
      - Philippines, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/242.R
      - Philippines, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3560)
  - Puerto Rico, 1951; 1951/243
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/243.A
      - Puerto Rico, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3561)
  - Texas, 1951; 1951/249
    - Texas, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3561)
  - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1951; 1951/258
    Pacific Islands
    - Marshall Islands, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3561)
  - South America, 1951; 1951/300
    - South America - Administration, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3562)
    - South America - Administration, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3563)
    - South America, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3564)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/300.A
      - South America, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3564)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/300.D
      - South America - McKel-1 - Nied-1, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3565)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/300.S
      - South America, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3564)
  - Argentina, 1951; 1951/301
    - Argentina, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3566)
  - Bolivia, 1951; 1951/303
    - Bolivia, 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3566)
  - Brazil, 1951; 1951/305
    - Brazil - (A-P), 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3567)
    - Brazil - (A-P), 1951 (Box 533, Folder 3568)
    - Brazil - Pinotti, Rafael V., 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3569)
    - Brazil - (R-Z), 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3570)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/305.A
      - Brazil, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3571)
  - Chile, 1951; 1951/309
    - Chile, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3572)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/309.A
      - Chile, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3572)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1951; 1951/309.C
      - Chile, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3572)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/309.D
      - Chile, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3572)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/309.E
      - Chile, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3572)
  - Colombia, 1951; 1951/311
    - Colombia, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3573)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/311.A
      - Colombia, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3573)
    - Colombia - Nursing, 1951; 1951/311.C
      - Colombia, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3573)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/311.D
      - Colombia, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3574)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/311.E
      - Colombia, 1951 (Box 534, Folder 3574)
  - Costa Rica, 1951; 1951/313
    - Costa Rica, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Costa Rica - Nursing, 1951; 1951/313.C
      - Costa Rica, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Costa Rica - Declinations, 1951; 1951/313.F
      - Costa Rica, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Costa Rica - Yellow Fever, 1951; 1951/313.O
      - Costa Rica, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Costa Rica - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/313.R
      - Costa Rica, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
  - Cuba, 1951; 1951/315
    - Cuba, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
  - Ecuador, 1951; 1951/317
    - Ecuador, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/317.D
      - Ecuador, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/317.E
      - Ecuador, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
  - Guatemala, 1951; 1951/319
    - Guatemala, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/319.D
      - Guatemala, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Guatemala - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/319.R
      - Guatemala, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
  - Haiti, 1951; 1951/320
    - Haiti, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
    - Haiti - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/320.E
      - Haiti, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3575)
  - Peru, 1951; 1951/321
    - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3576)
  - Mexico, 1951; 1951/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3576)
    - Mexico, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3577)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/323.D
      - Mexico, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3577)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/323.E
      - Mexico, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3577)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/323.R
      - Mexico, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3577)
  - Panama, 1951; 1951/327
    - Panama, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3578)
    - Panama - Yellow Fever, 1951; 1951/327.O
      - Panama, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3578)
  - Paraguay, 1951; 1951/329
    - Paraguay, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3578)
  - Peru, 1951; 1951/331
    - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3578)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/331.A
      - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3578)
    - Peru - Nursing, 1951; 1951/331.C
      - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3579)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/331.D
      - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3579)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/331.E
      - Peru, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3579)
  - El Salvador, 1951; 1951/333
    - Salvador, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Dominican Republic, 1951; 1951/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
    - Dominican Republic - Malaria, 1951; 1951/335.I
      - Dominican Republic, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Uruguay, 1951; 1951/337
    - Uruguay, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3580)
  - Venezuela, 1951; 1951/339
    - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
    - Venezuela - Nursing, 1951; 1951/339.C
      - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
    - Venezuela - Yellow Fever, 1951; 1951/339.O
      - Venezuela, 1951 (Box 535, Folder 3581)
  - Great Britain, 1951; 1951/400
    - Great Britain, 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3582)
  - England, 1951; 1951/401
    - England - (A-H), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3583)
    - England - (A-H), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3584)
    - England - Huxley, Julian, 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3585)
    - England - (I-01), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3586)